<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Digital-marketing</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Digital-marketing</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle"> </string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>

    <string name="menu_content">Contents</string>
    <string name="menu_favorite">Favorites</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_share">Share</string>
    <string name="menu_communicate">Support</string>
    <string name="content_item_dummy">Contents</string>
    <string name="frame_1_title">What is Internet Marketing?</string>
    <string name="frame_1_text_1">Internet marketing is knowledge (skills) that help to work with electronic channels (SEO, SMM, contextual advertising) and attract customers from the Internet.</string>
    <string name="frame_1_text_1_1">Where to increase the budget, how to correctly calculate the profitability of each traffic flow to the site.</string>
    <string name="frame_1_text_2">Now internet marketing is all about profit and making decisions about a particular ad.</string>
    <string name="frame_2_title">How to create an online business? We study competitors</string>
    <string name="frame_2_text_1">Before creating a website, it is recommended to study all the competitors on the Internet in your region. For example a niche: radio-controlled toys. We study competitors: direct and indirect and write down the advantages and disadvantages.</string>
    <string name="frame_2_text_2">Find competing sites using the seranking.com</string>
    <string name="frame_2_text_3">We go to each of the sites and carefully study the unique selling proposition (USP) and the structure of the sites:</string>
    <string name="frame_2_text_4">Abbreviated example of an analysis of a company selling RC models https://www.rcplanet.com</string>
    <string name="frame_2_text_5">Conclusions: it is better to start with 5–10 categories in order to create a wider range of products on the site. It is possible to work on pre-order for new models entering the market. To study what details for models users order. Having an offline store will inspire more confidence.</string>
    <string name="frame_2_text_11">We create a website</string>
    <string name="frame_2_text_12">We create a business card website or online store. You can start with a website builder, it is much faster and cheaper. The site will already be optimized for mobile devices, fast loading pages and payment by plastic cards.</string>
    <string name="frame_2_text_13">And you will receive the first orders within 2–5 days after development. First, buy a domain and link to a website builder:</string>
    <string name="frame_2_text_14">Domain binding will contribute to promotion, memorability and in the future will simplify the possible transfer of the site to your own CMS. You can buy a domain using the link https://godaddy.com</string>
    <string name="frame_2_text_15">Add more customer reviews, case studies, numbers. It is important to inspire trust in the prospect and create value for the product.</string>
    <string name="frame_2_text_16">Setting goals</string>
    <string name="frame_2_text_17">Ideally, we connect a separate phone for each channel with details on requests from contextual advertising in order to understand which requests are profitable and periodically review and disconnect non-working ones.</string>
    <string name="frame_2_text_18">Site test using contextual advertising</string>
    <string name="frame_2_text_19">After we have created a website or a group on social networks (Instagram, Facebook) and set up goals, then we test it for conversion using paid advertising: google adwords, advertising on Facebook or Instagram.</string>
    <string name="frame_2_text_20">Be sure to include remarketing in google adwords, facebook. We use retmarketing (pursuit) to catch up with users who have already visited our site.</string>
    <string name="frame_2_text_21">Each repeated contact with our site increases the opportunity to purchase a product or service. Remarketing increases loyalty to your brand and makes the total cost of applications / calls from the site cheaper. Use remarketing!</string>
    <string name="frame_2_text_22">Setting up contextual advertising at the start is better to order from freelancers. Then you will gradually learn this tool, including communicating with a freelancer.</string>
    <string name="frame_2_text_23">You can find an freelancer on the sites:</string>
    <string name="frame_2_text_24">You can start with an advertising budget of $ 200- $ 300 per month. After a month of testing, you should understand the cost of the application for each of the advertising channels and understand your profit, ROI and draw conclusions.</string>
    <string name="frame_2_text_25">After talking on the phone with clients and studying the applications from your site, an understanding of the target audience (gender, age, demography) will come. This information will be useful for adjusting advertising campaigns in google adwords, facebook.</string>
    <string name="frame_2_text_26">In addition to gender and age, you can increase the rates for mobile users.</string>
    <string name="frame_3_text_1">SEO (search engine promotion)</string>
    <string name="frame_3_text_2">SEO (search engine promotion) is an action aimed at improving the visibility of a site in search engines. The main goal is traffic from Yandex and Google search engines.</string>
    <string name="frame_3_text_3">Site preparation plan upon creation:</string>
    <string name="frame_3_text_4">SEO audit</string>
    <string name="frame_3_text_5">After creating and filling the site with content, it is recommended to perform a seo audit. For correcting h1 headers, titles, content, redirects, removing broken links, etc.</string>
    <string name="frame_3_text_6">Tools:</string>
    <string name="frame_3_text_8">Commercial factors</string>
    <string name="frame_3_text_9">For commercial sites, it is important to indicate phone numbers in a prominent place on the site. Also, the presence of the page contacts with the indication of telephones, e-mail, addresses, maps.</string>
    <string name="frame_3_text_10">How to get more traffic?</string>
    <string name="frame_3_text_11">We create a blog (information section) and write articles on our topic. A minimum of 30 articles per month is recommended. Better 100 articles per month, you can order on the exchange - https://www.etxt.biz</string>
    <string name="frame_3_text_12">Examples of blogs:</string>
    <string name="frame_3_text_14">Links</string>
    <string name="frame_3_text_15">After creating and optimizing the project, it is recommended to test it using contextual advertising for 1–2 months, then, having understood the profitable categories, the products should start working with the link mass.</string>
    <string name="frame_3_text_16">It is better to buy links for related topics and your region, then related topics and the general region. For example: a real estate agency in New York. We buy links on all sites in New York and everything related to real estate in New York and throughout the United States.</string>
    <string name="frame_3_text_17">To buy we use link exchanges with a one-time payment for a link:</string>
    <string name="frame_3_text_18">It is better to use anchors (link text) like:</string>
    <string name="frame_3_text_19">This will protect you from anchor spam in links. You can spend from $ 300 per month on links. Buying them on the main page and categories / subcategories that are profitable and are in the top 10 aisles, which brings them closer to the top 1.</string>
    <string name="frame_3_text_20">For the pros, you can study the link mass of competitors using - https://ahrefs.com</string>
    <string name="frame_3_text_21">Checking positions and traffic</string>
    <string name="frame_3_text_22">Every 2 weeks you can check positions using - https://topvisor.com</string>
    <string name="frame_4_text_1">Contextual advertising</string>
    <string name="frame_4_text_2">Contextual advertising is ads (text, image, video) that are shown to users in accordance with their search queries, interests or behavior on the Internet. Contextual advertising is shown in search engines, on various sites, in mobile applications, etc.</string>
    <string name="frame_4_text_3">If you are planning to launch contextual advertising in Yandex Direct or google adwords for the first time, we recommend that you contact specialized specialists.</string>
    <string name="frame_4_text_4">You can find an artist on the sites:</string>
    <string name="frame_4_text_5">Self-study google adwords:</string>
    <string name="frame_4_text_6">PPC courses:</string>
    <string name="frame_5_text_1">SMM (social media promotion)</string>
    <string name="frame_5_text_2">List of steps to launch campaigns:</string>
    <string name="frame_5_text_3">Instagram promotion:</string>
    <string name="frame_5_text_4">Promotion in Facebook:</string>
    <string name="frame_5_text_5">Useful books on the topic</string>
    <string name="frame_6_text_1">Content marketing</string>
    <string name="frame_6_text_2">Content marketing is the distribution of useful content that is not direct advertising, but which indirectly convinces the audience to make the necessary decision to purchase a product or service.</string>
    <string name="frame_6_text_3">The ways of distributing information content can be very diverse: sites, blogs, social networks, books, magazines, podcasts, seminars. Valuable content should be unique and useful.</string>
    <string name="frame_6_text_4">Content Marketing Goals</string>
    <string name="frame_6_text_5">How to launch successful content marketing</string>
    <string name="frame_7_text_1">Analytics</string>
    <string name="frame_7_text_2">Web analytics is a set of tools for collecting and analyzing the behavior of visitors on the site. Based on the data, the site is improved, advertising campaigns and sales plans are changed.</string>
    <string name="frame_7_text_3">Why do you need web analytics?</string>
    <string name="night_mode">Night mode</string>

    <string-array name="content_items">
        <item>1. Internet Marketing</item>
        <item>2. How to create a business on the Internet?</item>
        <item>3. SEO</item>
        <item>4. Context</item>
        <item>5. SMM</item>
        <item>6. Content-marketing</item>
        <item>7. Analytics</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="ads_app_pub">ca-app-pub-3188774017991247~4436530694</string>
    <string name="ads_app_unit_id">ca-app-pub-3188774017991247/3287100556</string>
</resources>